Antoine Ouellet

41 Lery Street Saint-Hubert (Quebec) J3Y 3Y2 Telephone: (438) 398-9392 Email: tonydude007@gmail.com

July 21st, 2023

Ladies and gentlemen,

It is with great pleasure that I wish to submit my application to you as a student in your organization.

I am currently looking to explore different fields of expertise with a link in my field of study. I am a student who learns very quickly and who can bring you a lot in your organization.

My mother tongue is French, but as I studied English for several years, my linguistic profile is completely bilingual. I am eager to learn, and I am sure you can contribute to my development.

Looking forward to working with you in the near future, I would ask that, ladies and gentlemen, accept this show of my sincerest feelings.

Antoine Ouellet

Antoine Ouellet

41 Lery Street Saint-Hubert (Quebec) J3Y 3Y2 Telephone:(438) 398-9392 Email: tonydude007@gmail.com

Language proficiency

French Mother tongue English Advanced

Academic

Institue Superieure en Informatique 2021 to Now

Montreal, Quebec

Champlain College, Computer Science Technology 2019 to 2021

Riverside, Quebec

Heritage High School 2017 to 2019

Saint-Hubert, Quebec

Dollard-des-Ormeaux School 2009 to 2017

Courcelette, Quebec

Rainbow School 2007 to 2009

Oromocto, New Brunswick

professional experience

Jean-Coutu Group Warehouse

Sept 2021 to now

Varennes, Quebec

- Driving Lifts
- Fufilling customer orders
- Verification of orders
- Shelf Restock

Grocery Clerk, IGA Vincent

April 2019 to August 2021

Longueuil, Quebec

- Receiving orders
- Filling shelves
- Customer Service
- Closure of the department

Cook, A&W

November 2017 to April 2019

Longueuil,Quebec

Preparation of meals and food

- Customer Service
- Cleaning and closing of the restaurant

Areas of expertise

computer science

- Microsoft Office: Word, PowerPoint
- Programmer : Java, Html, CSS
- Building Computers
- Configuring, managing, maintaining computers

Training

2014 to 2017 A&W training and food service hygiene training

2016 First Aid Courses with the Canadian Forces

Personal characteristics

- reliable
- Team spirit
- Ability to learn quickly
- autonomy
- Sense of responsibility
- Organizational sense

Awards and honours

- 2015 to 2017 Grand Défi Pierre Lavoie La Course
- 2017 Prix « Outstanding School Spirit Trophy » Dollard-des-Ormeaux school
- 2017 Nominated Cadet-Master (Cadet Corps 2772)
- 2016 Leadership Award (Pine River activity) Dollard-des-Ormeaux school

References will be provided upon request